Do you like it?
You son of a bitch!
Why did you lie to me?
I'm not some random person
whom you can fool with your campaign!
Your family would smile at me,
but in fact, you all look down on me!
You act so high and mighty,
but you're such an asshole!
I'm sorry?
Fuck you!
Eva?
Eva!
I'm sorry.
I should have been
more understanding and supportive,
about you and Grandma.
You can rest assured
that Nicole and I are just friends.
There's no one in my heart but you.
Are you still mad at me?
If something is bothering you, we can talk.
Please say something.
The other day...
an officer asked Domino about you and Ginny.
An officer?
That's strange.
I saw him in front of the hospital,
and he said nothing.
Do you know what he asked her about?
When you were in the US,
it was the same time as when Ginny was there.
And?
So what? What's the matter?
Many people in my parties visited the US
at the same time.
The officer needed to question everyone,
don't you think so?
Come on, he was just doing his job
and I helped him.
I have nothing to hide anyway.
Don't worry about me.
Excuse me, I think I should go.
I kept her company
while Domino was running some errands.
Sure, feel free to leave.
Okay.
Wait.
I think I need to practice more.
I feel like I didn't do well enough.
Sure.
Eva.
But I'm here to take you to dinner.
I'm not free today.
I have a lot to do.
- Let's do this.
- Sure.
Sorry about that.
Were you okay earlier?
Why are you asking me this?
Nothing. You just looked so tense earlier,
when...
Never mind.
Do you want to practice, or...
you just want to be alone?
I'll go and sit over there.
Let me know when you feel better.
Hey.
Take your time.
What's the matter? Why are you so quiet?
Hey! Hey!
What's wrong?
Eva, what is it?
Are you still mad at Wee?
What?
Is this...
Book said that I should know about this.
So, are you going to see her?
I am.
I'm so furious.
But I kept quiet about this,
because I want to know more from Book first.
Hey, I... I need to confess something.
What?
I also heard about Wee's behavior.
About?
I also heard that he was dating someone else.
But I had no idea it was Ginny.
Why didn't you tell me?
Eva.
You're not stupid.
You chose to ignore it, didn't you?
And I had no evidence.
If I had told you, you would be mad at me.
What's next?
What are you going to do?
I decided to stay with him...
Because I always believed
that he was loyal to me.
And that he loved only me.
I will go and meet Book.
I'll ask her about Ginny's trip to New York
and compare it with Wee's trip schedule.
If I'm certain that he had cheated on me,
I will break up with him.
This is weird for me,
to see another me standing right here
and staring back at me.
Hey.
What? I didn't watch anything.
What do you mean?
It's late, you should go to bed.
So you can recover faster. Okay?
It's not that late. It's only 8 PM.
Hello, Book? Where should we meet?
We need to talk in the car.
I don't want anyone to find out
that we had met up.
It is that bad?
You need to see it yourself,
and you'll understand.
I got this package from someone
after Ginny passed away.
They rang the bell and just dropped it off.
Did you know that it was Wee?
Ginny said that she dated a politician,
but it was seven to eight months ago.
Do you know who sent you these?
If I were to guess,
I think it was her stalker who attacked you.
He was stalking her
even before she was famous.
He knew everything about Ginny,
and used to dig up Ginny's trash
in front of her house.
He hired a photographer who lived there
to take these photos for him.
Can I keep these photos?
I'm going to burn them after this.
Why do you need them for?
If the photos are leaked,
we all will be in big trouble.
Honestly,
if I had known that Ginny was dating Wee,
I would have stopped her.
He's a well-known player.
Weechai and Weechana are half-siblings.
People my age know it well
how dangerous the Chaichana family can be.
Back then,
Weechai's mother disappeared without a trace.
If you continue to date him,
I think you need to be cautious.
You should have told me you were coming,
so I could prepare
something delicious for you.
I don't want you to be too tired.
No, I won't. I cook every day.
Come on, honey. Let's go inside.
Are you hungry?
Let's go inside.
Did you eat something?
Here it is, your favorite dessert.
Let's eat.
You want me to feed you?
Oh my! You cheeky girl!
You work in action films,
but the moment you come home,
you ask me to feed you.
Oh my!
Here.
Is it good?
Are you tired?
What is going on?
Who hurt you?
What?
It's okay.
It's okay. It's gonna be okay.
It's okay, I'm right here.
It's okay.
You will be okay.
What is going on?
I've never seen you cry like this.
Who hurt you?
I've decided to break up with Wee.
Good for you! Thank you for doing this.
You will finally be out of his circle.
You won't find happiness dating a politician.
True, he's wealthy,
but I'm sure it comes with a price.
Why did you decide to break up with him?
We are not going to make it.
His family won't accept me.
And he has someone else.
Good for you! You made the right choice.
You need to be with someone
who appreciates your true value.
If he doesn't appreciate you,
you need to leave.
Look at me,
if I closed my shop for even a day,
our neighbors wouldn't have anything to eat.
I can't live anywhere else.
You need to be in a place
where people will appreciate you.
If nobody loves you, I still love you.
Hey, Auntie.
I may not be able to see you for a while.
I need to practice my fighting
and English-speaking skills.
Please take care of yourself.
If you're too exhausted, you need to rest.
If you need some sleep, you need to get some.
You have money to spend,
so you don't have to be busy all the time.
You need to say it to the girl in the mirror.
I want to be good in what I do.
You are already good in what you do.
I want to be the Number 1 superstar.
Sure, you can.
Yes, you can, and you will.
You're my superstar.
Hello.
Eva, can I see you for a bit?
I don't like it that we argued.
I don't think I can see you.
Why's that?
I feel a little bit under the weather.
I feel like I'm having a fever.
Sure, if you say so.
You should get some rest first.
I understand.
Sir?
Are you going to ask Eva and Pie
to help you out with your campaign?
That's right.
Do you know about Pie and her friends' rate
for the event?
I'll handle it.
You need to ask the locals,
ask them if they can help us in any way.
Yes, sir.
Eva.
Where have you been?
I went to see my aunt.
Why didn't you tell me?
I called you, but you didn't answer.
I'm sorry.
I had a lot on my mind,
and I just ended up driving to her place.
So he really was dating Ginny?
Yeah.
I've decided to break up with Wee.
Honestly, I kinda knew
that he probably was dating someone else too,
judging from the circle that he was in.
I'm not okay about this.
I'm not okay,
that he was dating Ginny or someone else.
I'm fine if we use the same makeup artist.
But I'm not okay
if we have the same boyfriend.
And I'm tired.
I'm tired of feeling
that I can never be good enough.
He's not worth my effort.
But he...
he isn't loyal to me.
Good.
Cut him out of your life completely.
When will you let him know?
As soon as possible.
I want to focus on my work.
I hope that my work will turn out great.
And I want to do this for myself.
I want people to say
that the role that I got is made just for me,
and that nobody can play this role but me.
Of course, you can do it.
You can do it.
If you feel like this is too much for you,
you need to tell me.
Thank you.
- Yo!
- Ready?
- Ready.
Are you?
Ready.
Okay, we'll focus on running at zone 2 pace.
So it won't be too exhausting for us.
Okay, then.
Shall we?
Meaning?
- Follow.
- What does it mean? Tell me!
Hurry.
- Come on.
- What did you say?
You use "Shall we?" when you invite someone
to do something with you.
Like, "Shall we go?" or "Shall we dance?"
You can also say,
"Would you like to?" or, "How about we?"
Or "Wanna go?",
or something else simple as "We move?"
You need to look at the context and situation
when somebody asks you as well.
If there're only just the two of you
and they ask, "Wanna go?"
You should ask them back, "Wanna go do what?"
"Do what exactly?"
Because the unclear invitation
could lead to...
something that is unhealthy.
Oh, I got it.
Like go partying? Or doing drugs?
Or sleeping together, right?
Yeah, something like that.
Wanna go?
Yes.
This is a river, Chao Phraya.
This is the Chao Phraya River.
You need to say the specific name first.
"River" only indicates what the place is,
like "street".
When you want to say the place,
you need to say its name first.
So it will be Chao Phraya River.
Like "Sukhumvit" and followed by "Street".
The way you say it will be different
from how you say it in Thai.
Gosh, so confusing.
Take your time, you don't need to rush.
Also, when you're talking about places,
you need to use "the", not "a".
The...
It's confusing.
Take it slow.
This is the...
The... what is it called?
Small river.
Close. We would call this "a canal".
A river is a natural stream of water.
When it is a man-made constructed water way,
we'd call this "a canal", not small river.
Kaa-nal.
- Try again?
- Canal.
It's pretty good.
Canal.
You speak Thai quite fluently.
I lived in Thailand until I was 16 years old.
My parents were in a car accident.
I had no one left but my uncle
who lived abroad.
So I needed to move there to live with him.
My dad left my mom.
After that, she passed away,
so I lived with my aunt.
I grew up with her street food business.
And I grew up in my uncle's kitchen.
Excuse me.
- Oh my!
- It's her!
- Can I take a picture with you?
- Okay.
Sure.
You're so pretty.
One... two... three.
You're not in the frame.
Can you take one for us?
- Take a picture for us?
- Right.
- Sure.
- Please get a wide shot.
Sure, got it.
Three... two... one.
Alright.
- Thank you.
Can I check them first?
- I want to know if they look great.
- So great.
- Eva, can we take a picture with you?
- Sure.
- Take one for me.
I'm still working out,
so I can't stay for long.
Can you all get in one frame?
I don't want to upset my personal trainer.
Ready?
Thank you.
Hello.
Hey.
You're so cute.
I'm running on my treadmill tomorrow.
I didn't expect so many people
would come to you.
See? I told you.
Why are you laughing? What did I say wrong?
Nope, it's great. You said it right.
Here.
Good job, let's go.
I met Eva during my morning run.
Huh? What's this?
I just died! I got to run close to Eva.
Eva is so cute.
Who is there with her? He's so hot.
Whoa! Who is running with Eva?
This is not the guy she dated with.
He's so hot, is he her personal trainer?
I like their chemistry.
Can I get his Instagram?
Oh, please people!
Stop your imagination right now.
We don't want to be in trouble.
Hey!
Eva, get in the car!
- Hurry!
- Where are we going?
I need to stretch first.
No need to. You need to go, now.
- What is going on?
- Pun, get in.
- What is wrong with you?
- Just get in.
What? I'm starting to get mad.
I was so busy
that I forgot
that you two shouldn't be
going out and jogging like this.
They posted it up so quickly.
What music did they play in the background?
What is going on?
People posted about us jogging in the park.
What?
You can't jog outside anymore.
If you want to jog outside,
I need to go with you,
or someone else needs to.
They are breaking the law.
I mean, they invaded our privacy.
We can't normalize this.
Welcome to my life.
I can't do anything about it.
Really?
I'll tell you about it when we're at the gym.
About what to do, and what not to do
when you're around Eva.
Who is he?
Her personal trainer.
He was the one
who saved her from the stalker.
You need to warn her
not to let it happen again.
People won't focus on our campaign
when there's news like this.
I need people to focus
mainly on our campaign, okay?
Got it.
Wee, we need to talk.
Did you see it?
I saw it.
Did she intentionally do that
because she was mad at you?
She didn't respect you at all.
Who's the guy?
Her personal trainer.
I think he was training her
according to the program.
I was about to talk to her about it myself.
But Dad said
that I needed to wait
until campaigning is over.
Is she that important?
You can't find someone else?
Everything is included
in the campaign planning already.
Our research team sees
that it will benefit us.
When we invited her
for the CSR event earlier,
it increased satisfied engagement
from our target household group.
Does she know how to behave appropriately?
I will talk to her about it.
You need to take care of it.
After the election,
you need to break up with her immediately.
Do you hear me?
Loud and clear.
[Ruam Thai Chana]
You have interviews
with two famous online magazines
this afternoon.
And the press conference of the campaign
is in the evening.
Reporters from all channels
will be joining the event.
Can you tell one of our reporters
to ask about Eva?
Sure. What topic will it be about, sir?
About her jogging with a guy this morning.
But sir...
Tell them to ask me
about how I felt when I saw the clips.
I'll tell them that I trust her
even though we are having some personal issues
at the moment.
They need to ask a follow-up question,
about the personal issues.
So I can say
that I'm too dedicated to my work,
and I have neglected people
who are close to me.
After that, there will be no more questions.
Got it, sir. I will take care of it.
[Pathumwan Metropolis Police Station]
[Police]
Sir?
What's up?
Can you buy me a cup of coffee?
Let's go.
My friend asked me to tell you this.
Ginny was drugged.
The reporter was also drugged
with the same drug last year.
It's the same type of drug.
Minimal use.
But they don't know the ingredients.
They're waiting for the lab result.
My friend from the forensic team said
that the symptoms should be
shortness of breath and foaming at the mouth.
Her bleeding should be
from contaminated chemicals left in her body.
What about the stalker that attacked Eva?
- He was released.
- What?
You didn't know?
We confiscated his computer and hard disk.
He paid the maximum fine and got released.
Where are the confiscated items?
In the evidence room.
Are you sure?
I'm not sure about that.
The cases were closed in strange way...
Both Ginny and the stalker's cases.
I heard that there were video clips
of Ginny getting cozy
with the new party's leader,
who is Eva's boyfriend.
It happened before the election.
What do you think?
Okay, two minutes easy,
one minute hard, okay?
Two minutes slow, one minute fast.
Then we alternate, okay?
Hey, I can't take it.
I know it's tiring, but this is the last set.
Come on, let's go.
Okay.
That's enough, good job.
Let's stretch.
Don't forget to get some protein.
You need it to repair your muscles.
I might need to read the script
and send it to the producer next week.
You got this. You will do great, I'm sure.
Boat will be taking off his cast tomorrow.
Then I can tutor you full time.
You can leave if you want to.
Domino will be here soon.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
I called you so many times.
You never answered
or returned any of my calls.
You were training that hard?
This is my job.
I know.
I'm not disturbing you.
I'm just worried about you.
Actually, I've been here for a while.
I tried to call you
and you didn't pick up your phone.
Let me give you a ride, come on.
It's okay.
- Domino will be here soon.
- Tell her to leave.
Hey, you! You need to leave.
Wee.
What's the matter?
- Get in the car.
- You can't do this to me.
I will show you what I can do.
- Come here.
- Let me go!
Hey! Stop! Stop!
- What is going on?
- Stop!
What is going on? Pun!
- Wee!
- Wee, you need to stop!
Can't you leave her in peace
for just one day?
Why do you need to get physical with him?
- What? What?
- Wee!
Pun! Pun!
Please, I beg you.
Let him go.
Assholes!
Damn it!
Asshole!
How the hell was I supposed to know, dude?
I heard you just got back
from overseas, didn't you?
- Yeah.
- From where?
- From New York, sir.
- New York, I see.